{
    "id": "161f527cfe514f48b979bf740a76c2ba",
    "title": "Infinitives Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The soup is ..................................... hot for me to drink.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b3f01e65dfe643e1a56a6a0c5d5389b7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The problem is ......................................... difficult for me to solve.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "very",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "25416eb7a2b148fe8e9e3c8093e3f6a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The grapes are .................................................. sour for us to eat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "46de5e0547f9419595eb148c3c976d59"
        },
        {
            "question": "Akbar propagated the Divine Religion ........................................... India.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "uniting",
                "to unite",
                "to uniting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e3f835105ed14e7cb5ed0f88c5e3045c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He worked hard ................................................. the promotion.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "getting",
                "to get"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dfb26a77fd27453fad445e9e911437dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "He went to the city ............................................... work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to find",
                "finding"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2013cc86c5e740638e412eb616453a66"
        },
        {
            "question": "The traveler sat down ................................................ some rest.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to get",
                "getting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "75dc5c386de0411ebd40f5388fb6e216"
        },
        {
            "question": "She opened her mouth ................................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to yell",
                "yelling"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "58ffd1fd9bf8448a818334269fb670ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "He picked up the gun .............................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shooting",
                "to shoot"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0062e043a69149d3b5537bf33e382933"
        },
        {
            "question": "I called him ...............................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "speaking",
                "to speak"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "83c668bc3d0e4ab6ad0190d134417aaa"
        }
    ]
}